Yes, hello everyone!
We are five mysterious people here today.
What are we going to do today?
Let's give Valentine's Day to our juniors!
Ta-da!
Until now, it's been a standard practice
But this time on YouTube, we're going to give Valentine's Day from seniors to seniors.
But this time on YouTube, we're going to give it to the juniors from the seniors!
Yay!
Everyone has a present of their own now!
And here are the five members.
What do you think they are?
I don't know.
I've been taking care of the fifth graders.
Most of you didn't get one.
She's the only one who got one.
Clooney got one and the seniors are using it.
I don't know...
We are the ones who didn't get it.
So it's a little bit humiliating.
I hope I can convey my usual feelings to everyone.
The 5th graders are really waiting for us, even though they don't know what we're going to do.
They're waiting for us, right?
So, I'm going to call up the girls who want to give a little bit.
I'm going to call out those who want to give a little bit.
Let's give it to them.
Yes, sir!
Let's go!
Now I'd like to go to see my drummer, who is a 5th term student. The members I want to give it to are
I personally like them a lot, and
I also like her in general.
I've seen her in everyday life, and she's a really, really strong girl.
I chose her because I wanted to express my feelings that I usually can't. I think she probably didn't expect this.
I don't think she is expecting this at all.
I'd like to go.
Is it closed? Closed?
It's open.
Oh, no.
It was an escape game.
An escape game.
May I go first?
Yes, so we have come to the front of the dressing room where your expectations await.
They are talking lively, but we are going in now.
I'm nervous. Are you okay?
Excuse me.
What? Someone's here.
Hi, I'm Umezawa.
Good evening.
Excuse me.
What should I do?
May I call one person?
Yes, ma'am.
There's something I need to talk to you about.
What for?
A call for you.
I'm a little nervous.
Did I do something wrong? I don't know.
What did you do? We're just having a nice talk.
Excuse me.
I'm gonna go in this room for a minute.
I'm about to cry. Why, why, why, why?
Are you dragging us into this too?
No, we're not involved, we're involved.
That's why I called Iroha. You didn't hear anything?
I didn't hear anything. I'm about to cry.
I'm about to cry. I haven't heard anything. I know, but today I'm giving Iroha a valentine.
Me? I called you because I wanted to give her a valentine.
Me? I'm sure you'll be surprised.
I hope she'll be pleased. Here you go. Thank you.
May I open it? Of course, of course.
What? I hope she'll like it.
Something's not right. Don't look.
Here we go. Oh, catflower.
Yes! I'm so happy!
Why are you so happy all of a sudden? I was planning to give a valentine to an unregulated senior.
I don't usually have much to say to people.
I like her a lot... personally... she's the embodiment of Nogizaka.
She's a really proper girl, and she's not embarrassed to be shown anywhere.
She's always working hard and always smiling at rehearsals.
I think she's going to be in more and more shows from now on, maybe even Romijuri.
I'm convinced that she's the kind of girl who will spread Nogizaka in various ways.
I'd like to support her in any way I can.
I'm happy too. Let's work hard and do our best.
I'll do my best.
I don't have much to say.
Thank you for listening to Fresmez.
He's back. He's back.
He's smiling.
What, what, what, what?
Yes, yes, 4:00?
Semya. The termlies I want to give you, sir.
I personally just wanted to give you something that I just wanted to give you.
I wish I could give you that as a gift.
Okay, I'll go.
Harkinz, hakinz.
Ready?
Yes, ma'am.
Hello. - Hello.
Good afternoon.
Good evening
Hi, good evening.
I wanted you to come even though I have a little.
Sorry. During the delivery.
I thought you might have guessed.
I can't see anything.
I'll leave it with you.
Here you go.
What's this?
Thank you very much.
I'm very nervous.
Why?
I'm nervous.
Oh, you know what I'm talking about. Wait a minute.
This is the worst.
How is this possible?
Oh.
I've got him.
What is it?
Today, you know, we did a Valentine's Day project from juniors to seniors,
Today, we have the opposite version,
I invited Arno.
I really wanted to give this to Arno,
It's not a big deal,
Thank you for your hard work as chairperson of Underlove the other night.
Also, he wants to get to know you,
He said, "Let's go to oden.
Let's go to oden.
And, yes.
I always tell them that I love them,
If you buy this...,
This one.
Actually, it's a hand-me-down. It's my book,
I heard that Arno sang Remisé at an event,
This is actually from when I went to London,
I found the sheet music at the L'émisé theater in London,
I used to practice with it,
I used to practice with it, but I don't use it anymore,
But I thought that I would not use it anymore, and I couldn't get it in Japan,
You can't find it in Japan, and it's not on the Internet,
I'm glad you got the sheet music.
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
Please sing well.
I really want to hear it. I just want to hear it.
Let's camon.
Please make use of it.
I'm back.
I'm scared of the way they look at me.
What's that?
I'll say something in English.
A word in English?
W
Straw.
It's not straw.
Yes, so which 5th term member would you like me to give you?
I would like to give it to the 5th term member.
Her voice, the way she stood there, her, I don't know, her gestures, everything.
I felt that she was very polite, and I felt that she was the only one I could not give a chance to.
I thought she was a wonderful girl, and I had been thinking about her for a long time.
I have a personal feeling of liking her, so I would like to go to her as soon as possible.
I want to go to you right away because I personally like you.
Once, I was sleeping a little bit today.
I was sleeping a little bit today, but you know, I've been doing everything.
But...
I love it!
Iroha!
Hey!
What's this?
I'm taking Iroha with me.
Me?
That's the most inaudible thing I've ever heard.
Everyone be quiet for a second.
Shoo!
I'm going right up to the wall!
Here we go.
I can't hear much but laughter.
That's why I brought Iroha.
You really scared me.
I was.
I'm surprised.
I'd like to give Iroha a Happy Valentine's Day.
Thank you very much.
I've always loved you from the beginning.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
I had contacted you a while ago,
I like Irohan's talent or sense of style,
I like your singing, your way of speaking, your voice, your performance,
I love your singing, but also the way you speak, your voice, and your performance.
I love her singing, but I also love the way she speaks, her voice, and her performance.
I thought it was wonderful that she had a direction that only Irohan could have,
So I gave it to him.
Thank you very much.
I feel so happy.
I can't believe it.
Thank you very much.
There are so many seniors who like Irohan,
I can't believe it.
Today I realized that you really think so,
I'm really happy.
I'm so happy.
The radio is here.
I made the radio in tech class at school.
I used a really weird one,
Was it great?
It was great.
I'm very happy.
I'm happy.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Let's be friends.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I'll go next.
I'd like to...
I'd like to give it to you.
We talk about all kinds of things a lot,
It's really easy to talk,
He told me that he doesn't need to worry about me.
I'm very happy to hear that,
I tried to get the cap for the construction work from many people, but none of them gave it to me,
I tried to make hats for many people during the construction, but I didn't receive any from any of them, and it ended a little sadly,
I'll be satisfied if I can convey my love to them this time,
I'll be happy if I can convey my love to them this time.
I'm going.
Drama of fantasy.
Indeed.
It's hard to bring them to a deserted island.
I'm in my fifth year.
Do you have any color?
I have a...
Here.
See?
I get carried away.
I'm going to do it because it's going to get the better of me.
It's not that loud.
I'm fine.
Oh, really?
You're getting better.
I'll pick coconuts from the tree for you.
But if I go with Hina, we'll fight for sure.
Why?
What kind of quarrel?
There are a lot of them.
What's that? Where are they?
Oh, there he is! Mr. Sachtar.
Excuse me.
Camoong.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
We're very similar, aren't we?
It's kind of close, close, close.
Four of a kind.
Very similar.
Yes, why did I call you?
I'm going to be pissed.
Pissed off?
I'm still thinking that maybe it's a sermon on the project of taking care of you.
That's too bad.
Is it too close?
This time it's Valentine's Day, the other way around.
Reverse Valentine's Day?
You chose it?
I'm glad.
I'm so happy!
Thank you for your hard work.
Then I'll give it to you first.
Mr. Sakuta, since the very beginning, you've told me many stories.
We talked about all kinds of things.
I felt very comfortable with him.
I hope we can continue to be friends in the future.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
I'm really happy to get your gift.
It's like a dream
We've been talking about going on trips.
I've always wanted to go on a trip.
I haven't been able to, so I want to.
I'm so happy that you said you don't care about me even if I don't say anything.
I'm so happy that you said that.
Ayame?
I'm the same way.
When I'm around younger students.
I feel like I have to talk.
But with Mr. Sakuta, I feel at ease even in silence.
It's rare to find someone like that.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
That's a good thought.
But I remember you.
My theory is...
Excuse me.
Yes, so I'd like to finish up with my fourth student, Kuromi Haruka, who would like to go to me.
I couldn't choose one, so I chose two.
The members of that group...
I'm going to give it to both of you.
I really like both of you.
I don't know, they are both really straight.
It's hard for them to tell other children about the pain they are going through
I feel that they tend to hold it in.
I know I'm not a very reliable senior.
I would like to give this to both of them.
I'd like to give this to both of them.
Well, I'm off now.
Thank you for your hard work.
Telepan and Sacchan...
May we ask you to come once?
Thank you for your hard work.
Two?
That's what I'm talking about.
There's a pattern.
What do you mean, "two"?
Yes, I mean...
What were they being chased for?
Did you figure it out?
This disappeared a while ago.
Actually, it was in there earlier.
Okay, so K is for sad and A is for cheerful.
Didn't you say you did?
I did.
I didn't mean happiness.
I meant happy.
Then I guess it's a happy thing.
Well, you know what?
It's a version from a senior member of the board of trustees.
I see.
Well, that's kind of what it is.
But of course, it's more than a project.
I wanted to convey my feelings properly.
I'd like to convey my feelings regardless of the plan.
I want to convey my feelings properly.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to give it to Sacchan.
Sacchan has a lot to say these days.
I've noticed that you've been talking a lot lately.
I've been keeping it bottled up inside of me.
I think there's a part of you that I've been keeping bottled up inside and haven't been able to show it to you.
I know I'm a little unreliable.
If there is anything else you need, I would be
I'd be happy to help.
I hope we can go out for dinner and talk about all kinds of things.
I'd like to give it to you.
Thank you very much.
It's like this.
So, the second Telepan is...
I'm the top student in the fifth grade.
Because he can do everything on his own.
I thought she might be difficult to rely on.
Also, she is a really straight girl.
I knew how hard she worked until midnight.
I wanted her to take care of herself first.
I also want her to continue to lead the 5th term students as a cool older sister.
I'll give it to you.
Thank you for everything.
I'm not used to being a cool older sister at all.
I'm just trying to be an older sister to the 5th term students.
I'm your big sister.
Thank you very much.
You're my big sister.
I'm glad.
Thank you
You make me blush.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
Is everyone here for the fifth term?
Yes, we are.
May I ask you all to gather here?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting, but I wanted to give something to everyone.
So I brought some for everyone.
This is for everyone.
Please give it to everyone.
Thank you very much.
I would like to end this project like this, so please continue to be my friend.
I'm sure there will be more opportunities to see the bond of Nogizaka at birthday live and other events, so we'll do our best so that everyone can see this bond.
Please subscribe to our channel and rate us highly!